

Ming-Yang Ho



ikaminyou@gmail.com

github.com/Kaminyou

in linkedin.com/in/kaminyou

+886 952792255

Summary ·

A data scientist at aetherAI with 4+ years of experience in 2D/3D computer vision, natural language processing, machine learning, and deep learning algorithms development.

Besides, I am also adept at web programming, cryptography, and clinical pharmacy.

Skills -

- Programming related
 - · Python
 - ·Cython
 - ·ReactJS
 - · C/C++
 - · MySQL
 - · Web security
 - Docker
 - ·Linux
 - ·Git
- Others
 - ·Adobe Ps/Ai/Id/Pr/Lr
 - Psychiatry
 - ·Clinical pharmacy

Language ·

- · Mandarin (native)
- ·English (TOEIC 825) [2014]
- · Japanese (JEPT N1) [2021]

Interests

Machine learning, Deep learning, Full stack development, Cyber security

Work experience

Data Scientist

aetherAI, Oct. 2021 - (Current)

Teaching Assistance (TA)

NTU EE Machine Learning, Feb. 2021 - Jul. 2021

NTU EE Web Programming, Feb. 2021 - Jun. 2021

NTU CSIE Bioinformatics and Cheminformatics, Sep. 2020 - Jan. 2021

Data Engineer (ML) Intern

Dcard, Jun. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- · Built an automatic image cropping system to attract users' attention.
- · Invented a malicious applicants detection system with SimCLR.
- · Established a system to immediately detect offensive comments.

Deep Learning Researcher Intern

Institute of Information Science, Academa Sinica, Jul. 2019 - Aug. 2019

· Leveraged the concept of RGB channels to assist in SNP prediction.

Honors

2021 PyCon APAC Speaker

Get 3D models out of nothing: Python implementation of deep learning-based 3D models reconstruction from 2D images..

2021 PyCon TW Speaker

Implementation of a deep learning-based saliency detection system by Python

2020 HITCON Speaker

Potential Security and Privacy Issues in Novel Taiwanese National eID system

Awards

2021 Outstanding Paper Award

Multi-label Classification on CT Medical Imaging Competition, 3rd prize ICH detection enhanced by asymmetric loss with CNN-LSTM approach.

Recent Projects

2021 SUPERB: Speech processing Universal PERformance Benchmark

Entrusted by NTU, CMU, MIT, and Facebook AI to build a leaderboard web server for SUPERB Benchmark. (https://superbbenchmark.org/)

2021 Template is all you need: 2D to 3D reconstruction with template learned by contrastive learning

Developed a 2D to 3D reconstruction DL model leveraging the template concept.

Education

2019~2021 Master of Science (@CSIE CMDM) GPA 4.20

Computer Science (bioinformatics specialization) *BEBI, National Taiwan University (NTU)*

Thosis

Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features

2014~2019 Doctor of Pharmacy GPA 4.06

Clinical Pharmacy

School of Pharmacy, National Cheng Kung University (NCKU)

Publications

Liu, L. C., Ho, M. Y., Su, B. H., Wang, S. Y., Hsu, M. T., & Tseng, Y. J. (2021). PanGPCR: predictions for multiple targets, repurposing and side effects. *Bioinformatics*, 37(8), 1184-1186.

Ho, M. Y., Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) A step toward practical digital markers for monitoring patients with Parkinson's disease using a deep-learning-based AI-assisted 3D camera system for gait assessment. *Clinical Parkinsonism & Related Disorders*. [under review]

Ho, M. Y., Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features. [unpublished manuscript]

Ho, M. Y., Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) A 2D camera is all you need: gait analysis with frontal-view 2D video by deep learning-based 3D estimation. [unpublished manuscript]